wpsubscribers.com 2014-12-16

# Privacy Policy | WPSubscribers - Premium Wordpress Subscription Plugin

## Privacy Policy

IMPORTANT! THIS PRIVACY POLICY (“POLICY”) DESCRIBES WPSUBSCRIBERS.COM, INCORPORATED PROTECTS, USES AND SHARES ANY INFORMATION WHICH IS PROVIDED BY YOU. BY ACCESSING THE SITE, YOU ARE INDICATING THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTOOD AND AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLCY AND OUR TERMS OF SERVICE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF SERVICE OR OUR PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE SITE OR ANY SERVICES OFFERED AT THE SITE.

You are granted a limited license to use this product. The product may be used or copied only in accordance with the terms of that license, which is described in the following paragraphs.

### Types of Information that WPSubscribers Collects

WPSubscribers collects two different types of information from You when You use the Site. We collect certain types of personally identifiable information from You (“Personal Information”) when You register a member or affiliate account (“Account”). We also collect certain non- personally identifiable, aggregate information from visitors to our Site regardless of whether they create or sign in to an Account (“Traffic Data”).

### Personal Information

Personal Information In order to create an Account You will have to provide Personal Information that may include: name, address, email address, telephone number, billing information (such as a credit card number), the type of personal computer being used to access the services, payment and tax withholding information… and WPSubscribers have a right to email you for our notification.

### Traffic Data

WPSubscribers may also use certain web technologies such as “cookies” to track Your use of our Site. Your browser may have an option that allows You to reject cookies, but doing so may limit Your use of our Site. Usage Information is anonymous and does not personally identify You. In addition, WPSubscribers may use web beacons or other tools to measure the effectiveness of, and otherwise manage, our online advertising. These web beacons enable our advertising server to recognise You when You visit the Site and to determine which banner ads bring users to the Site. WPSubscribers does not use spyware, adware or any other similarly intrusive software. The Usage Information that WPSubscribers collects depends on how You choose to use this Site.
